&gt；&gt；Steve：我们将玩一段时间。
&gt;&gt; Steve: We're gonna play with this for
a little bit.
我们将看看这个例子。
We're gonna take a look at this example.
&gt；&gt；Steve：我们将转到页面，非常酷。
&gt;&gt; Steve: We'll go to the page, very cool.
这是一个非常愚蠢的例子，它使用了一堆div，并且
This is a really silly example
that takes a bunch of divs, and
你可以按下这个双倍大小的按钮，你知道会发生什么吗？
you can hit this double-sized button,
and you know what's gonna happen?
它们都会变大一倍。
They're all going to double in size.
哇，很疯狂，对吧？
Whoa, crazy, right?
我是一个数据可视化专家，好吧，[笑]。
I'm a data visualist, all right, [LAUGH].
这很酷，我现在正在做数据可视化。
It's very cool, I'm doing data vis now.
它们的大小都是原来的两倍。
And they all double in size.
我要你做的就是启动你的Chrome工具
What I want you to do is fire
up your Chrome Tools, and
继续，点击这里的性能按钮，这里的性能标签。
go ahead and hit this Performance button
here, the Performance tab up here.
看到这个小录音按钮了吗？
And see this little record button?
你会碰到它，它会录下来
You're gonna hit that,
and it's gonna record and
你要把栅栏扩大一倍。
you're gonna double the size of the bars.
一次，两次，三次。
One time, two times, three times.
然后，我们会看看在那之后我们从工具中得到了什么。
And then, we're gonna look at what we
got from the tools right after that.
所以让我给你们大约三分钟的时间来做这件事
So let me give you about
three minutes to do that and
然后我们一起来看看，你先来探索一下。
then we'll kind of look at it together,
and you kind of explore it first.